https://electronicscity.com/index.php/privacy-policy

Default welcome msg!
Search:
Search
Cart 0 item
Shopping Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Home
My Account
My Wishlist
My Wishlist
Quisque iaculis rhoncus orci eu suscipit lorem sodales at. Fusce ac metus ut metus adipiscing dapibus ut ac leo.
Login
Forgot Your Password?
New Customer ?
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better, protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the ElectronicsCity.Com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by going to the ElectronicsCity.Com Site and login in with your password into our secure server. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error to customerservice@electronicscity.com .
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (800) 866-5033 or send us an email at privacy@electronicscity.com
Newsletter
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Subscribe
Info
About Us
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Free Shipping
Help
Help Center
Customer service:1.800.866.5033
ElectronicsCity.Com ©Copyright 1999-2020 ElectronicsCity.Com| Powered by SunShop "Shopping Cart Software"
Master Card Secure Code Verified Visa Visa Master Card Paypal
Back to Top
Magento Theme Variations
Google Fonts
Import these google fonts
ABeeZee
Abel
Abhaya Libre
Abril Fatface
General Font
Font for body, content, text...E.g. normal 12px/1.55 Oswald, "Helvetica Neue", Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif
H1
E.g. normal 22px/1.15 Oswald,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif
H2
E.g. normal normal 20px/1.25 Oswald,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif
H3
E.g. normal 18px/1.25 Oswald,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif
H4
E.g. normal 16px/1.35 Oswald,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif
H5
E.g. normal 14px/1.35 Oswald,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif
H6
E.g. normal 13px/1.35 Oswald,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif
Page Background Pattern
Specify background pattern image.
Page Background Position
Property Values: left top, left center, left bottom,right top, right center, right bottom,center top,center center,center bottom,x% y%, xpos ypos, inheritDefault: 0 0
Page Background Repeat
Property Values: repeat, repeat-x, repeat-y, no-repeat, inherit Default: repeat
Header
Header Background Color
Default #ffffff
Header Text 2 Color
Default: #7c97bf
Header Line Color
Default: #dcdcdc
Header Background 2 Color
Header Background Pattern
Specify background pattern image.
Header Background Position
Property Values: left top, left center, left bottom,right top, right center, right bottom,center top,center center,center bottom,x% y%, xpos ypos, inheritDefault: 0 0
Header Background Repeat
Property Values: repeat, repeat-x, repeat-y, no-repeat, inherit Default: repeat
Top Menu
Top Menu Background Color
Default #ffffff
Top Menu Text Color
Default: #323232
Top Menu Line 2 Color
Default: #000000
Top Menu Hover/Active Background Color
Body Background Pattern
Specify background pattern image.
Body Background Position
Property Values: left top, left center, left bottom,right top, right center, right bottom,center top,center center,center bottom,x% y%, xpos ypos, inheritDefault: 0 0
Body Background Repeat
Property Values: repeat, repeat-x, repeat-y, no-repeat, inheritDefault: repeat
Box Shadow
Default: 0 0 5px #e0e0e0
Rounded Corner
Default: 3px
Footer
Footer Background Color
Default #ffffff
Footer Text 2 Color
Default:#646474
Footer Background 2 Color
Default #f1f1f1
Footer Text 1 Color
Default #323232
Footer Background Pattern
Specify background pattern image.
Footer Background Position
Property Values: left top, left center, left bottom,right top, right center, right bottom,center top,center center,center bottom,x% y%, xpos ypos, inheritDefault: 0 0
Footer Background Repeat
Property Values: repeat, repeat-x, repeat-y, no-repeat, inheritDefault: repeat
[profiler]Memory usage: real: 10485760, emalloc: 7494192Code ProfilerTimeCntEmallocRealMem
